http://www.ipge.com/privacyPolicy

Privacy Policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.ipge.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices. We have agreed to advise you of:
1.       what personally identifiable information is collected from you through our web site;
2.       the organization collecting the information;
3.       how the information is used;
4.       with whom the information may be shared;
5.       what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your personally identifiable information;
6.       the types of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and
7.       how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should contact us at ipgeseminars@ipge.com.
Information Collection and Use
We use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. IPGE, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on our website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.
Registration
In order to purchase products offered through our website, a user must first complete a registration form. As part of this Registration Form, a user will be required to give their contact information (name, address, phone number and email address), as well as financial information (a valid credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to complete a transaction. If we have trouble processing an transaction, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. Whenever you provide sensitive information (for example, a credit card number), we will take reasonable steps to protect it, such as encrypting your card number. We will also take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage.
Cookies
To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers, strategic partners). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information (e.g., age, income, online shopping preferences) for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.We use an outside financial institution to process credit card payments. This institution does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Additionally, we will forward certain personally identifiable information (name, address) to vendors (airlines, hotel, car rental company) from whom you have purchased products or services. Except for the foregoing, we will not share any personally identifiable information with any third parties.
Links
Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by IPGE, Inc. on this website.
Security
We are proud of our commitment to protecting your privacy online. We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every month, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to ipgeseminars@ipge.com.
Special Offers
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires to be a member of our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our registration form has an "opt-out" mechanism so users who utilize our services, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.Members who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at ipgeseminars@ipge.com.Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally revise or update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
How to Contact Us
We welcome comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information, and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure. Should you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding our privacy policy, send an e-mail to us at ipgeseminars@ipge.com.
Address : PO Box 28 Hastings, Michigan 49058-0028 | Email: ipgeseminars@ipge.com
Copyright IPGE | Privacy Policy
"fast cache""site_page_cache inactive""cacheStatus:1""Page Not Cached""site_page_cache inactive""cacheStatus:1""Page Not Cached"
